#### Contact

Tunis-montfleury +21653573786 (Mobile)

abdoumed46574423@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/djeibaba

abdellahi-142968235-abdellahi-

(LinkedIn)

Top Skills

machine learning

Deep learning

IOT

Mobile Applications

Web Applications

API Development

## Languages

Français (Full Professional)

Anglais (Full Professional)

Arabe (Native or Bilingual)

### Certifications

Big Data Vs Data Science

Internet of Things (IoT):

Fundamental Course (101 level)

Web Development Bootcamp

Big Data Programming Languages &

Data Analytics, Storage, Mining &

Visual Big Data Technologies

AutoML Automated Machine Learning BootCamp (No Code ML)

python programming

# Djeibaba Abdellahi

Advanced Technology Engineer

Grand Tunis Metropolitan Area

# Summary

I specialize in advanced technology, particularly in AI data processing, with a strong focus on emerging technologies such as smart grids, AI analysis, IoT, machine learning, deep learning, computer vision, NLP and Web Developement.

You can find detailed descriptions of real projects I have undertaken on my GitHub: https://github.com/khayidjeibab?tab=repositories

# Experience

## **Groupe SFM**

Al Software Engineer

February 2024 - Julie 2024 (4 monthes)

Gouvernorat Tunis, Tunisie

\*Engineering Internship\*

Energy Disaggregation Based on Unsupervised Learning (Detection of Active or Inactive Electrical Appliances from Their Electrical Signatures Using Unsupervised Learning).

## **Groupe SFM**

Electronics and Automation Specialist February 2023 - August 2023 (7 months)

Gouvernorat Tunis, Tunisie

\* Professional Master's Degree Internship\*

Design and Implementation of an Autonomous Smart Home with Camera Surveillance (Al & IOT)

#### **SOMELEC**

Software Application Engineer April 2021 - July 2021 (4 months)

Nouakchott, Mauritania

\*Bachelor's Thesis Internship\*

Development of an API interface for managing a solar park connected to the grid

#### **IBS**

Wep developper September 2019 - December 2019 (4 months) Mauritania

\*volunteer internship\*

Development of mobile applications for publishing the company's products

# Education

Higher School of Engineering in Tunis

Engineering, Advanced Technology · (September 2022 - July 2024)

Université Tunis Carthage

Master's degree, Electronics, Electrical, and Automation · (September 2021 - May 2023)

University of Nouakchott Al Aasriya

Bachelor's Degree, advanced technology Systems · (September 2019 - 2021)